* [* Scholarship Search
            
            College scholarships you qualify for.](https://www.scholarships.com/scholarship-search)
    * [* College Matches
            
            Personalized list of colleges that fit you.](#)
    * [* Student Loans
            
            Explore loan options to help pay for college.](https://www.scholarships.com/financial-aid/student-loans)
    * [* Blog
            
            Expert advice to help pay for college.](https://www.scholarships.com/blog)
    
    * [* Scholarship Directory
            
            Find scholarships by category.](https://www.scholarships.com/financial-aid/college-scholarships/scholarship-directory)
    * [* College Search
            
            Find the college that's right for you.](https://www.scholarships.com/college-search)
    * [* Student Resources
            
            Top resources for your scholarship journey.](https://www.scholarships.com/student-resources)
    * [* Calculators
            
            Calculate your cost to attend college.](https://www.scholarships.com/financial-aid/calculators)

    * [* Scholarship Search
            
            College scholarships your child qualifies for.](https://www.scholarships.com/scholarship-search?regtype=parent)
    * [* College Matches
            
            Personalized college list that fits your child.](#)
    * [* Student Loans
            
            Explore loan options to help pay for college.](https://www.scholarships.com/financial-aid/student-loans)
    * [* Blog
            
            Expert advice to help pay for college.](https://www.scholarships.com/blog)
    
    * [* Scholarship Directory
            
            Find scholarships by category.](https://www.scholarships.com/financial-aid/college-scholarships/scholarship-directory)
    * [* College Search
            
            Find the college that's right for your child.](https://www.scholarships.com/college-search)
    * [* Student Resources
            
            Top resources for your child's scholarship journey.](https://www.scholarships.com/student-resources)
    * [* Calculators
            
            Calculate your cost to attend college.](https://www.scholarships.com/financial-aid/calculators)

    * [* Educators Home
            
            Learn how we can help you and your students.](https://www.scholarships.com/educators)
    * [* Educator Log In
            
            Log in to your educators account.](https://www.scholarships.com/educators/login)
    * [* Educator Resources
            
            Free resources for educators.](https://www.scholarships.com/educators/guidance-resources)

    * [* Submit a Scholarship
            
            Share your scholarship with eligible students.](https://www.scholarships.com/scholarship-providers-resources/list-your-scholarship)
    * [* Provider Log In
            
            Log in to your scholarship provider account.](https://www.scholarships.com/scholarship-providers-resources/list-your-scholarship/login)
    * [* Guidelines
            
            Guidelines for submitting a scholarship.](https://www.scholarships.com/scholarship-providers-resources/scholarship-provider-guidelines)

* Student **Log In**

* Students

    * [* Scholarship Search
            
            Get matched to scholarships you qualify for.](https://www.scholarships.com/scholarship-search)
    * [* Scholarship Directory
            
            Find scholarships by category.](https://www.scholarships.com/financial-aid/college-scholarships/scholarship-directory)
    * [* College Matches
            
            A personalized list of colleges that fit you.](#)
    * [* College Search
            
            Find the college that's right for you.](https://www.scholarships.com/college-search)
    * [* Student Loans
            
            Explore loan options to help pay for college.](https://www.scholarships.com/financial-aid/student-loans)
    * [* Student Resources
            
            Top resources for your scholarship journey.](https://www.scholarships.com/student-resources)
    * [* Blog
            
            Expert advice to help pay for college.](https://www.scholarships.com/blog)
    * [* Calculators
            
            Calculate your cost to attend college.](https://www.scholarships.com/financial-aid/calculators)
    
* Parents

    * [* Scholarship Search
            
            College scholarships your child qualifies for.](https://www.scholarships.com/scholarship-search?regtype=parent)
    * [* Scholarship Directory
            
            Find scholarships by category.](https://www.scholarships.com/financial-aid/college-scholarships/scholarship-directory)
    * [* College Matches
            
            A personalized college list that fits your child.](#)
    * [* College Search
            
            Find the college that's right for your child.](https://www.scholarships.com/college-search)
    * [* Student Loans
            
            Explore loan options to help pay for college.](https://www.scholarships.com/financial-aid/student-loans)
    * [* Student Resources
            
            Top resources for your child's scholarship journey.](https://www.scholarships.com/student-resources)
    * [* Blog
            
            Expert advice to help pay for college.](https://www.scholarships.com/blog)
    * [* Calculators
            
            Calculate your cost to attend college.](https://www.scholarships.com/financial-aid/calculators)
    
* Educators

    * [* Educators Home
            
            Learn how we can help you and your students.](https://www.scholarships.com/educators)
    * [* Educator Log In
            
            Log in to your educators account.](https://www.scholarships.com/educators/login)
    * [* Educator Resources
            
            Free resources for educators.](https://www.scholarships.com/educators/guidance-resources)
    
* Scholarship Providers

    * [* Submit a Scholarship
            
            Share your scholarship with eligible students.](https://www.scholarships.com/scholarship-providers-resources/list-your-scholarship)
    * [* Provider Log In
            
            Log in to your provider account.](https://www.scholarships.com/scholarship-providers-resources/list-your-scholarship/login)
    * [* Guidelines
            
            Guidelines for submitting a scholarship.](https://www.scholarships.com/scholarship-providers-resources/scholarship-provider-guidelines)

Student **Log In** [Student **Sign Up**](https://www.scholarships.com/scholarship-search)

Log In

* * *

New to Scholarships.com?

**Header text...**

Any secondary text...

Should there be privacy and TOS here?

[About Us](https://www.scholarships.com/about-us) > Privacy Policy

Updated: March 5, 2024

Privacy Policy
==============

[](javascript:openWindow('http://www.bbb.org/chicago/business-reviews/scholarships-and-financial-aid/scholarshipscom-in-highland-park-il-53000345');)

This Privacy Policy applies to [www.scholarships.com](http://www.scholarships.com/). This Privacy Policy describes how Scholarships.com collects and uses the personal information you provide. It also describes the choices available to you regarding the use of, your access to, and how to update and correct your personal information.

Scholarships.com recognizes that your privacy is important. To demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy and to explain the types of information we obtain about visitors to our website, how that information is obtained and used, and how visitors can restrict its use or disclosure, we have created the Privacy Policy below. The following discusses our information gathering and dissemination practices at Scholarships.com.

Information We Receive and How It Is Used
-----------------------------------------

All personal information obtained by Scholarships.com about individual visitors to our website is information supplied voluntarily by that visitor. During registration, users are required to provide certain categories of information, such as name, address, email address, phone number, a password, date of birth, gender, and country of citizenship. In addition, users may choose to provide other categories of information, such as career objectives, health or disability information, hobbies, and other interests. Scholarships.com encourages users to provide all fields of information to maximize the effectiveness of the scholarship and college search. We ask for permission when sharing information with marketing partners, which are reputable companies and organizations that provide products and services of interest to students and parents. Users may choose whether to opt-in or opt-out of sharing information with our marketing partners.

When Scholarships.com shares personal information with a third party, the information will become permanently subject to the information use and sharing practices of the third party. The third party will not be restricted by our Privacy Policy, with respect to its use and further sharing of your personal information. If you agree to receive communications from our marketing partners and later change your mind, you will need to contact those companies directly. Any information updates you wish to make must be forwarded to the company at that point in time.

Upon request Scholarships.com will provide you with information about whether we hold any of your personal information. Users may change personal profile information at Scholarships.com at any time by logging in to the website and entering the email address and password associated with their profile. After users have logged in, they will be directed to their Scholarship Matches. In the tabbed navigation at the top of the page, users will find a link to "Profile". By clicking on that tab, users will be directed to a summary of their information, divided into sections. An "Edit This Section" option in the upper-right corner of each section allows users to modify and update their information. Users can also [contact us here](https://www.scholarships.com/about-us/contact-us/privacy-policy) in order to request access to submitted information. To protect the security and integrity of our users’ information, we will take necessary steps in verifying all new profile identities before providing access. It is the responsibility of the user to make all necessary changes in their profile and make sure their profiles are up-to-date.

Users of Scholarships.com who wish to terminate their membership, or otherwise request to cease usage of their information at Scholarships.com may do so at any time by contacting us via our contact form by [clicking here](https://www.scholarships.com/about-us/contact-us/account-updates-and-questions "Website Content"). Please be sure to type "Remove" in the subject field and submit the email account associated with the membership you would like terminated. We will respond to your request within a reasonable timeframe. Information will be retained for as long as the account is active or requests our services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

Scholarships.com is committed to safeguarding users' privacy on our website. We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once it is received. We require our employees to protect our users and visitors by keeping their profile information private, and expect our marketing partners to follow suit. Rest assured that your user profile will be protected when you visit Scholarships.com. There are security measures to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of all user information under our control.

Regardless of whether you wish to share your personal information, we reserve the right to share aggregated demographic data and related information with our business partners. Such aggregate information will not contain any personal information that can identify any individual user.

Information Sharing & Email Preferences
---------------------------------------

Scholarships.com understands the importance of protecting personally-identifiable information. We will not share, sell, rent or otherwise transfer any information without the user's permission, and then, only in accordance with the terms set forth in this Privacy Policy. Our website provides users the opportunity to unsubscribe/opt-out from receiving email messages from Scholarships.com and its marketing partners, or from having their personal information shared with our marketing partners. Users may change their email preferences by following the unsubscribe instructions contained in each of the email messages they receive or by [clicking here](https://www.scholarships.com/about-us/privacy-policy/unsubscribe "Unsubscribe"). Please allow up to seven business days for these changes to take effect. If you no longer wish to be a registered user of Scholarships.com, you may have your profile removed by [clicking here](https://www.scholarships.com/about-us/contact-us/account-and-notification-settings "Email Unsubscribe").

Scholarships.com may periodically use contact information in order to send emails regarding updates at the Scholarships.com site, such as scholarship opportunities and additional listings. The frequency of these messages will vary depending on the user's preference, including the types of scholarships and other activities in which a user has indicated an interest. If you specifically provide Scholarships.com with permission at the time of registration, you may also receive commercial emails. Please note that email messages from third parties are not governed by the opt-out provisions of this Privacy Policy.

In certain situations, Scholarships.com may be required to disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities. We may also disclose your personal information as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process. When we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request.

We may provide your personal information to company provider services that help us with business-related activity; such as shipping your order or offering customer service. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only on a service-needs basis.

California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA)
--------------------------------------

**Right to Know:** you have the right to know whether Scholarships.com has collected personal information from you. You may submit up to two requests within a 12-month period for access to or disclosure of the specific pieces of personal information collected about you in the last 12 months, free of charge. You may request access from Scholarships.com for any of the following:

* The categories or specific pieces of personal information that Scholarships.com has collected from you;
  
* The categories of sources from which Scholarships.com has collected your information;
  
* The business purpose for which the information was used; and
  
* The categories of third parities with which Scholarships.com shares personal information.

**Right to Delete:** you have the right to request, up to two times in a 12-month period, that Scholarships.com delete any of your personal information that Scholarships.com has collected from you, subject to certain exceptions.

**Right to Opt-Out:** you have the right to opt out of Scholarships.com sharing your personal information to third parties. You also have the right to opt out of Scholarships.com’s sale of your personal information.

**Right to Correct:** you have the right to request Scholarships.com correct inaccurate personal information.

**Right to Non-Discrimination:** Scholarships.com will not discriminate against you for exercising your privacy rights.

**Request to Remove Information:** you or your authorized agent may submit a request to access or delete your personal information or opt out of Scholarships.com’s sharing or sale of your personal information by [contacting us here.](https://www.scholarships.com/do-not-sell-my-personal-information)

**Access, Update or Delete Information:** you can access or update your personal information at any time by logging into the Scholarships.com website and selecting “Profile”. You may delete your account by [contacting us here.](https://www.scholarships.com/about-us/contact-us/account-and-notification-settings)

Collection of Passive Information
---------------------------------

As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically. This information may include Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data.

We, Scholarships.com, and our partners use cookies or similar technologies to analyze trends, administer the website, track users’ movements around the website, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. You can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level, but if you choose to disable cookies, it may limit your use of certain features or functions on our website or service.

Some of our business partners, such as advertisers, use cookies on our site, but we have neither access to, nor control over, these cookies. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Scholarships.com only and does not cover the use of cookies by our business partners

We partner with a third party ad networks to display advertising on our web site. Our ad network partners use cookies and web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information about your activities on this and other web sites to provide you targeted advertising based upon your interests. If you wish to not have this information used for targeting ads, you may opt-out by [clicking here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/). Please note this does not opt you out of being served advertising. You will continue to receive generic ads.

We use Google AdSense to publish ads on this site. When you view or click on an ad a cookie will be set to help better provide advertisements that may be of interest to you on this and other web sites. You may opt-out of the use of this cookie by visiting Google’s Advertising and Privacy page: [http://www.google.com/privacy\_ads.html](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

We may share statistical and demographic information about our website's visitors with our marketing partners. This information is only provided in the aggregate; meaning that the information is about our website's visitors as a group and not about individually-identifiable visitors.

Public Forums
-------------

Our Web site offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. Please be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, you may contact us by [clicking here](https://www.scholarships.com/about-us/contact-us/account-updates-and-questions "Account Updates & Questions"). In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information. In these situations, we will provide you with an explanation.

Social Media Features
---------------------

Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button. These Features may collect your IP address, page visitation on the site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing them.

Links to Other Websites
-----------------------

Scholarships.com contains text and banner links to other sites. Scholarships.com does not exercise control over the information, products, services or policies of third party companies accessible through our site. This Privacy Policy applies solely to the information collected by this site

Collection of Information from Children
---------------------------------------

Scholarships.com abides by federal law and the guidelines set up by the Federal Trade Commission regarding youth privacy. As such, Scholarships.com will not knowingly collect any personally-identifiable information from children under the age of 13, nor will children under the age of 13 be allowed to register with Scholarships.com.

Notification of Changes
-----------------------

If we are going to use your personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection, we will notify you via email prior to the effective change. You may decide whether or not we can use your information in this manner. In addition, if we make any material changes to our Privacy Policy that do not affect user information already stored in our database, we will post a prominent notice on our website notifying users of the change. In cases where we post notice of changes, we may also email users who have opted to receive communications from us, notifying them of the changes to our privacy practices.

In the event that Scholarships.com sells, signs or transfers some or all of its business to a successor or acquirer, Scholarships.com may sell, assign or transfer all of your information, regardless of your opt status, to such successor or acquirer.

Testimonials
------------

We post user testimonials on our website, all of which are volunteered and none of which contain individually-identifiable information beyond the user's first name, last initial, and photograph. Each user is made aware of the purpose of their supplied testimonial that it will be published on Scholarships.com. Users are under no obligation to participate, and we obtain the user's consent prior to posting this information. If you have any questions about a testimonial you can contact us by [clicking here](https://www.scholarships.com/about-us/contact-us/account-updates-and-questions "Website Content & Membership").

Scholarships.com has adopted privacy principles that state our commitment and define policy on safeguarding visitor and user privacy when conducting business. Questions regarding this Privacy Policy statement, the practices of this website, or dealings with Scholarships.com should be directed to Scholarships.com's [privacy department](https://www.scholarships.com/about-us/contact-us/privacy-policy "Privacy Policy"). Alternatively, you may contact us at:

Privacy at Scholarships.com  
Scholarships.com, LLC  
513 Central Avenue, Suite 300  
Highland Park, IL 60035

Channels

Scholarships

College

Help

Copyright © 1998 - 2024 Scholarships.com All Rights Reserved  
Scholarships.com Publisher
